[{"question": "  guys, guys, i've got great news! guess what\u009a", "answer": " uh, ah, monica's pregnant?!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s9/ep15.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 1, "asentId": 2}, {"question": "  really?  let's get past the moment.", "answer": " what's your news?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s9/ep15.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 3, "asentId": 4}, {"question": "  oh, honey, that's incredible!", "answer": "  gosh, what's the pay like?  oh, come on people\u009a  come on, now, if i don't know who makes the most, how do i know who i like the most!  hey joey!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s9/ep15.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 7, "asentId": 8}, {"question": " actually, it pays nothing. it's an internship.", "answer": " oh, that's cool. we have interns at 'days of our lives'.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s9/ep15.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 9, "asentId": 10}, {"question": " so, uh, what kinda stuff do you think they'll have you do there?", "answer": " well, it's a training program, but at the end, they hire the people they like.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s9/ep15.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 13, "asentId": 14}, {"question": "  that's great.", "answer": " yeah, i mean, there's probably gonna be some ground work which will probably stink, you know, grown man getting people coffee is a little humiliating", "docId": "friendsCopy/s9/ep15.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 15, "asentId": 16}, {"question": " you know, if i didn't already have a job, i think, i would have been really good in advertising.", "answer": " ross, you did not come up with \"got milk?\"", "docId": "friendsCopy/s9/ep15.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 19, "asentId": 20}, {"question": "  hey!", "answer": " hey!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s9/ep15.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 23, "asentId": 24}, {"question": " he just left.", "answer": "  who did?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s9/ep15.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 27, "asentId": 28}, {"question": "  joey! you never gonna believe it: she called.", "answer": "  she did?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s9/ep15.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 29, "asentId": 30}, {"question": "  you got it!", "answer": "  i did?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s9/ep15.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 31, "asentId": 32}, {"question": " what is she talking about?", "answer": " i don't know, but it sounds great.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s9/ep15.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 33, "asentId": 34}, {"question": " your agent called. you got that audition.", "answer": " with lennart haze?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s9/ep15.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 35, "asentId": 36}, {"question": " yes.", "answer": " oh my god, that is great! that is *** for a play on broadway\u009a and in a real theatre, not that little one underneath the dally like last time.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s9/ep15.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 37, "asentId": 38}, {"question": " is it a good play?", "answer": " well, it must be, because i read and i didn't understand a singe word.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s9/ep15.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 39, "asentId": 40}, {"question": " yeah, and lennart haze is starring in it\u009a", "answer": " yeah, yeah, and directing.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s9/ep15.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 41, "asentId": 42}, {"question": "  he was so good in that movie of macbeth.", "answer": "  you saw that?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s9/ep15.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 43, "asentId": 44}, {"question": " no, but\u009a i saw the previews. they played it right before jackass. rachel and joey:  ah!", "answer": " yeah, he's done some amazing works.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s9/ep15.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 45, "asentId": 46}, {"question": " oh, yeah. oh, i loved him in those cell phone commercials.", "answer": "  i know. when the monkey hits him in the face with that giant rubber phone.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s9/ep15.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 47, "asentId": 48}, {"question": " hey! maybe the monkey will be at the audition!", "answer": "  don't make me more nervous than i already am!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s9/ep15.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 49, "asentId": 50}, {"question": "  good morning, everybody.", "answer": " can i get you a cup of coffee, sir?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s9/ep15.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 51, "asentId": 52}, {"question": " oh, no, no, i'm an intern, just like you guys\u009a except for the tie, the briefcase\u009a and the fact that i can rent a car.", "answer": " seriously, you're an intern?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s9/ep15.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 53, "asentId": 54}, {"question": " yeah, well, i'm kinda heading into a new career direction and, you know, you gotta start at the bottom.", "answer": "  dude!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s9/ep15.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 55, "asentId": 56}, {"question": " the comedian? uso?!", "answer": "  uhm, it's usa, sir.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s9/ep15.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 59, "asentId": 60}, {"question": " it is so amazing to meet you.  i'm such a big fan of your work.", "answer": " well, i've\u009a i've been blessed with a\u009a a lot of great roles.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s9/ep15.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 63, "asentId": 64}, {"question": " tell me about it! \"unlimited nights and weekends!\"", "answer": " you making fun of me? because i am not a sell-out.  i didn't do that for the money, i believe in those phones. i almost lost a cousin because of bad wireless service.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s9/ep15.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 65, "asentId": 66}, {"question": " no, i-i-i wasn't making fun of you, honestly, i-i think you were great in those commercials.", "answer": " really?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s9/ep15.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 67, "asentId": 68}, {"question": " yeah.", "answer": " well, i do bring a certain credibility to the role.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s9/ep15.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 69, "asentId": 70}, {"question": "  are you kiddin'? when they shoot you out of that cannon\u009a", "answer": " peeeeeooooooooch  \"hang up that phone!\" one take!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s9/ep15.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 71, "asentId": 72}, {"question": " wow!", "answer": " so, shall we read?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s9/ep15.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 73, "asentId": 74}, {"question": " oh, yah, sure.", "answer": " top of act two. this is my entrance. you got it?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s9/ep15.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 75, "asentId": 76}, {"question": " err, \"i think you know\".", "answer": " \"bastard\"!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s9/ep15.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 79, "asentId": 80}, {"question": " \"i am what you made me. you know what? i could go right now.\"", "answer": " \"go, go!\"", "docId": "friendsCopy/s9/ep15.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 81, "asentId": 82}, {"question": " \"i can't. oh, i want to, long pause, but i can't.\"", "answer": " i'm sorry, sorry. you're not supposed to say \"long pause\"", "docId": "friendsCopy/s9/ep15.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 83, "asentId": 84}, {"question": " no. thank you so much for coming in. we appreciate it, thank you.", "answer": " ah, y-y-you're sure you don't want me to do it again? i could do it with an accent, you know, southern  \"i could go right now, maaan!\"", "docId": "friendsCopy/s9/ep15.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 87, "asentId": 88}, {"question": "  ah, hi, ah. thank you so much for whispering for my benefit, but, ah, look, if you just tell me what i did wrong, i'd just love to work on it and come back and try it again for you. and, and also:  'how you doing?'  you should, please, just gimme another chance. i really wanna get better, please.", "answer": " well, if you wanna come back at the end of the day today, here are my notes. ready?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s9/ep15.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 97, "asentId": 98}, {"question": " yeah.", "answer": " uhm, you're in your head. you-you're thinking way too much.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s9/ep15.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 99, "asentId": 100}, {"question": " i really doubt that.", "answer": "  no, no, no. it's that you're not connected with anything in your body. there's no urgency. the scene is a struggle, uhm, it's a race. also, what you did was horizontal. don't be afraid to explore the vertical. and don't learn the words. let the words learn you.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s9/ep15.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 101, "asentId": 102}, {"question": " hey, do you wanna go to dinner tonight?", "answer": " oh, i can't. i've got a date with that waitress, katy, yeah, i know we've been only going out like twice, but i have a really good feeling about her.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s9/ep15.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 105, "asentId": 106}, {"question": " alright. just give me your wallets and there won't be a problem.", "answer": "  what?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s9/ep15.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 109, "asentId": 110}, {"question": " alright, lady, now give me your purse!", "answer": " no.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s9/ep15.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 115, "asentId": 116}, {"question": " lowell, is that you?", "answer": " phoebe?  oh my god!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s9/ep15.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 119, "asentId": 120}, {"question": "  i'm sorry, ross, this is my old friend lowell from the streets. lowell, ross.", "answer": " ross, nice to meet you.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s9/ep15.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 123, "asentId": 124}, {"question": " yeah, a real pleasure.", "answer": " ah, it's been so long, so long.  i can't believe you're still doing this!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s9/ep15.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 125, "asentId": 126}, {"question": " ough, i know, but i quit smoking!", "answer": " good for you!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s9/ep15.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 127, "asentId": 128}, {"question": " so you look like you're doing really well! i guess you're mugging days are behind you?", "answer": " ouh\u009a", "docId": "friendsCopy/s9/ep15.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 129, "asentId": 130}, {"question": "  oh my god. phoebe, you used to mug people?", "answer": " excuse me, ross, old friends catching up\u009a", "docId": "friendsCopy/s9/ep15.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 131, "asentId": 132}, {"question": " hey, how did the audition go?", "answer": " well, they wanna see me again this afternoon, but, err, well, lennart haze did not like me.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s9/ep15.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 133, "asentId": 134}, {"question": " what happened?", "answer": " well, he said i wasn't urgent enough, you know, and that everything i did was horizontal and i should be more vertical. oh, and he said that i should think less.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s9/ep15.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 135, "asentId": 136}, {"question": "  honey, i'm old!", "answer": "  what's wrong?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s9/ep15.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 139, "asentId": 140}, {"question": " i am so much older than these other interns. i can't compete with them.", "answer": " so you're a little older. try to look at the positive: you have all this life experience.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s9/ep15.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 141, "asentId": 142}, {"question": " wooooooooow  it's like they're on fire!", "answer": " what are they?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s9/ep15.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 145, "asentId": 146}, {"question": " they're these prototype sneakers and come up with ideas on how to sell them which i can't do because no self-respecting adult would ever where these.", "answer": "  i give you $ 500 for them!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s9/ep15.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 147, "asentId": 148}, {"question": " what am i supposed to do with these?", "answer": " ah, come on, sneakers are easy. you wear sneakers all the time.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s9/ep15.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 149, "asentId": 150}, {"question": " well, first of all, they're not called \"sneakers\" anymore. apparently, they're called \"kicks\" or \"skids\" and i think i heard somebody say \"slorps\".  and here, look: they've got these wheels to pop out from the bottom so you can roll around 'cause, apparently, walking is too much exercise. kids, kids, roll your way to childhood obesity!  would you help me try to sell these?", "answer": " okay, have you considered using a girl with huge knockers?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s9/ep15.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 151, "asentId": 152}, {"question": " no, i don't think that's the kinda thing they're looking for.", "answer": " hey, that'd work on me! why did i get to buy mrs. butterwords?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s9/ep15.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 153, "asentId": 154}, {"question": " hey, hey!", "answer": " hey, you'll never guess what just happened\u009a phoebe and i got mugged!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s9/ep15.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 155, "asentId": 156}, {"question": " you okay?!", "answer": "  yah, because phoebe knew the mugger!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s9/ep15.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 157, "asentId": 158}, {"question": "  how do you know a mugger?", "answer": " i'm sorry i have friends outside the six of us.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s9/ep15.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 159, "asentId": 160}, {"question": " you wanna know how she knew him?  because phoebe used to mug people.", "answer": "  seriously?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s9/ep15.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 161, "asentId": 162}, {"question": " well, i'm not proud of it, but, you know\u009a sometimes when i was living on the street and i needed money for food and stuff i\u009a", "answer": "  phoebe, that is awful!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s9/ep15.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 163, "asentId": 164}, {"question": " well, ok, i wasn't rich like you guys, ok, i didn't eat gold and have a flying pony\u009a i had a hard life, my mother was killed by a drug dealer\u009a", "answer": " you're mother killed herself!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s9/ep15.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 165, "asentId": 166}, {"question": " she was a drug dealer!", "answer": " well, anyway, it was a good thing phoebe knew the knew him, because  i was about to do some serious damage!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s9/ep15.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 167, "asentId": 168}, {"question": "  okay\u009a", "answer": " well, this must've brought back some really bad memories for you, ross.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s9/ep15.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 169, "asentId": 170}, {"question": " why?", "answer": " well, ross was mugged as a kid.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s9/ep15.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 171, "asentId": 172}, {"question": "  you were?", "answer": " yeah, it was pretty traumatic. i was outside st. marc's comics\u009a you know, i-i-i was just there minding my own business, you know, seeing what kinda trouble spiderman got into that week-", "docId": "friendsCopy/s9/ep15.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 173, "asentId": 174}, {"question": "  wonderwoman!", "answer": " anyway, i was heading towards this bakery, you know, to pick up a couple of dozen linzer torts for someone\u009a  \u009a when outta nowhere this thug with a pipe jumps out and says: \"gimme your money, punk!\"", "docId": "friendsCopy/s9/ep15.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 175, "asentId": 176}, {"question": "  oh my god\u009a", "answer": " i know! and-and the worst part was they took my backpack which had all the original artwork i had done for my own comic book: \"science boy\"", "docId": "friendsCopy/s9/ep15.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 177, "asentId": 178}, {"question": " oh yeah! what was his superpower again?", "answer": " a superhuman thirst for knowledge.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s9/ep15.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 179, "asentId": 180}, {"question": " that's it.", "answer": " well, i-i better get to class  are there any more of your friends i should look out for on my way, phoebe?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s9/ep15.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 181, "asentId": 182}, {"question": " okay, i think we have a problem here.", "answer": " what?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s9/ep15.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 185, "asentId": 186}, {"question": " well, uhm, back in my mugging days, you know, i, uhm, i worked st. marc's comics.", "answer": " yeah?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s9/ep15.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 187, "asentId": 188}, {"question": " well, a pipe was my weapon of choice and, uhm, pre-teen comic book nerds were my meat.", "answer": " so?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s9/ep15.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 189, "asentId": 190}, {"question": " well, there was this one kid who had a sticker on his backpack that said- phoebe and monica: \"geology rocks!\"", "answer": " oh my god!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s9/ep15.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 191, "asentId": 192}, {"question": " you're late!", "answer": "  i know, i'm sorry, but can i just have a quick second to run to the bathroom?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s9/ep15.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 195, "asentId": 196}, {"question": " no, lennart doesn't wait!", "answer": " but i'm bursting with u-hu!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s9/ep15.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 197, "asentId": 198}, {"question": "  joey! here we go. let's go very quickly!", "answer": " actually, i really need\u009a", "docId": "friendsCopy/s9/ep15.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 199, "asentId": 200}, {"question": "  we must go now, quickly, please.", "answer": " yes\u009a ahahaaa", "docId": "friendsCopy/s9/ep15.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 201, "asentId": 202}, {"question": " ready? \"what the hell are you still doing here?\"", "answer": "  \"i think you know!\"", "docId": "friendsCopy/s9/ep15.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 203, "asentId": 204}, {"question": " \"oh, you sick bastard!\"", "answer": " \"i am what you made me! you know what?\"", "docId": "friendsCopy/s9/ep15.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 205, "asentId": 206}, {"question": " \"what?\"", "answer": " \"i could go right now.\"", "docId": "friendsCopy/s9/ep15.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 207, "asentId": 208}, {"question": " \"then go, go!\"", "answer": "  \"i, oh, i can't. i want to, but i can't!\"", "docId": "friendsCopy/s9/ep15.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 209, "asentId": 210}, {"question": " cut! that was good.  that was very good. you did everything i asked for.", "answer": "  i did?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s9/ep15.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 211, "asentId": 212}, {"question": " yes. plus\u009a what you've got that\u009a i don't know what you've got going\u009a this squirmy quality that you bring into the character that i couldn't've even imagined. wow, hey, here's what we gonna do: come back tomorrow for the final callbacks with the ***, do all of this what you've got going now, but \u0096 you know what? \u0096 more, more. can you do that?", "answer": " sure, yeah. i don't have time to say thank you because i really gotta go.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s9/ep15.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 213, "asentId": 214}, {"question": " hey!", "answer": " hey!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s9/ep15.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 217, "asentId": 218}, {"question": " what are you doing?", "answer": " putting on the sneakers\u009a thought i'd get into a younger mindset, you know, to see if it sparked anything\u009a", "docId": "friendsCopy/s9/ep15.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 219, "asentId": 220}, {"question": " oh, anything yet?", "answer": " yes, how's this: they're so uncomfortable it's like getting kicked in the nuts for your feet!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s9/ep15.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 221, "asentId": 222}, {"question": "  hey!", "answer": " hey!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s9/ep15.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 223, "asentId": 224}, {"question": " probably wanna know what i'm doing\u009a?", "answer": " no, that seems about right.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s9/ep15.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 225, "asentId": 226}, {"question": " yesterday at my audition, i really had to pee, and apparently, having to pee makes me a really good actor. i got a call-back, so i'm drinking everything. oh, by the way, that egg nog in our fridge was great!", "answer": " joey, that was formula.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s9/ep15.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 227, "asentId": 228}, {"question": "  you know what\u009a these aren't half-bad!  you should suggest something like these to ralph lauren.", "answer": " okay, first of all, that's stupid and second of all, i'm not allowed to talk to ralph.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s9/ep15.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 231, "asentId": 232}, {"question": "  hey, you!", "answer": " hey!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s9/ep15.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 237, "asentId": 238}, {"question": " hey, how was class?", "answer": " no one ever asked me that, what's wrong?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s9/ep15.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 239, "asentId": 240}, {"question": " nothing, i really wanna know.", "answer": " oh\u009a  well, uhm, there was actually a rather lively discussion about the pleistocene\u009a", "docId": "friendsCopy/s9/ep15.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 241, "asentId": 242}, {"question": "  alright, nothing is worth this. uhm, i have a confession to make\u009a uhm, okay, you know, that girl that mugged you when you were a kid\u009a", "answer": "  wh-what are you talking about? it wasn't a girl. it was this huge dude.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s9/ep15.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 243, "asentId": 244}, {"question": " you don't have to lie anymore, ross, i know that it was a fourteen year-old girl.", "answer": " no, it wasn't.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s9/ep15.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 245, "asentId": 246}, {"question": " yes, it was.", "answer": " no, it wasn't. you don't think i would've defended myself against a fourteen year-old\u009a", "docId": "friendsCopy/s9/ep15.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 247, "asentId": 248}, {"question": "  \"gimme your money, punk!\"", "answer": "  oh my god, it was you! i can't believe it, you\u009a you mugged me?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s9/ep15.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 249, "asentId": 250}, {"question": "  yeah, and i'm so, so sorry, ross, i'm sorry, but, you know, if you think about it, it's kinda neat.  i mean, well, it's just that i i've always felt kinda like an outsider, you know, the rest of you have these connections that go way back and, you know, now, you and i have\u009a have a great one!", "answer": " it's not the best!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s9/ep15.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 251, "asentId": 252}, {"question": " i know, i'm sorry, please forgive me. i don't know what to say\u009a", "answer": "  there's nothing you can say. that was the most humiliating thing that ever happened to me.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s9/ep15.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 253, "asentId": 254}, {"question": " really? even more humiliating than\u009a", "answer": "  hey, let's not do this!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s9/ep15.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 255, "asentId": 256}, {"question": " \u009a and then, at the end of the commercial, the girls get out of the hut tub and start making out with each other!", "answer": "  that's interesting! just one thought: you didn't mention the shoes. who's next?  chander\u009a", "docId": "friendsCopy/s9/ep15.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 257, "asentId": 258}, {"question": " okay\u009a  you start on the image of a guy putting on the shoes. he's about my age\u009a", "answer": "  your age?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s9/ep15.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 259, "asentId": 260}, {"question": " a-huh. so he's rolling down the street and he starts to lose control, you know\u009a maybe he falls\u009a maybe hurts himself. just then, a kid comes flying by wearing the shoes. he jumps over the old guy and laughs, and the line reads: \"not suitable for adults!\"", "answer": " chandler, that's great!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s9/ep15.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 261, "asentId": 262}, {"question": " you see? that has a clear selling point. it appeals to our key demographic, it's\u009a.  you did you come up with that?", "answer": "  i don't know, i don' i don' know! i was just trying to get into a young mindset, you know, and it just started to flow.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s9/ep15.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 265, "asentId": 266}, {"question": " that is great. good work! chandler. thank you.", "answer": " see all of you tomorrow.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s9/ep15.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 267, "asentId": 268}, {"question": " hey, ross!  i know you're still mad at me, but can i just talk to you for a second?", "answer": " sure, go ahead. whoops, sorry, sure, go ahead.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s9/ep15.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 271, "asentId": 272}, {"question": " oh my god.  i never thought i'd see this again.  it's all here. what made you save it all these years?", "answer": " i can't say, i just thought it was really good\u009a and\u009a maybe would be worth something some day.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s9/ep15.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 279, "asentId": 280}, {"question": " you really thought \"science boy\" was worth saving!", "answer": " yeah\u009a but you should know, i also have a jar of vaseline and a cat skull in here.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s9/ep15.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 281, "asentId": 282}, {"question": " still\u009a this is amazing\u009a oh my god, thank you, phoebe.", "answer": " you're welcome. and thank you for \"science boy\". i learned a lot from him", "docId": "friendsCopy/s9/ep15.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 283, "asentId": 284}, {"question": "  \"i need an answer!\"", "answer": " \"i-i-i can't tell you somethin' i don't know.\"", "docId": "friendsCopy/s9/ep15.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 287, "asentId": 288}, {"question": " \"you know!\"", "answer": " \"i don't know!\"", "docId": "friendsCopy/s9/ep15.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 289, "asentId": 290}, {"question": " \"i need an answer now!\"", "answer": " \"alright, here, you want an answer\u009a the answer\u009a is\u009a\"", "docId": "friendsCopy/s9/ep15.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 291, "asentId": 292}, {"question": "  oh!", "answer": " \"she never loved me, she only loved you.\"", "docId": "friendsCopy/s9/ep15.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 293, "asentId": 294}, {"question": " \"you knew this all along and you never told me? you never told me? i can never forgive you, i can never forgive myself, i have nothing to live for \u0096 bang \u0096 end scene!\"", "answer": " absolutely amazing!  the part is yours.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s9/ep15.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 295, "asentId": 296}, {"question": "  oh thanks, thanks! now, i really have to get\u009a", "answer": " wa-wa-wa-wait! congratulations! you did it! you did it!  you can relax now. yeah.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s9/ep15.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 297, "asentId": 298}, {"question": " wow, that's a big cable bill! huh, you don't have a job, but you have no problem ordering porn\u009a on a saturday afternoon?!  i was in the house!", "answer": "  hey, uhm, phoebe didn't by any chance mention that\u009a", "docId": "friendsCopy/s9/ep15.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 299, "asentId": 300}, {"question": " \u009a that she was the huge guy that mugged you? yah.", "answer": " i see. you didn't happen to tell\u009a", "docId": "friendsCopy/s9/ep15.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 301, "asentId": 302}, {"question": " \u009a everybody we know? yeah.", "answer": " great. thanks!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s9/ep15.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 303, "asentId": 304}]